lakeside.com 2004-08-04

# The Lakeside Collection(sm) - Affordable Gift Giving ideas for all occasions, and for yourself. Value Priced gifts for birthdays, Christmas, Halloween, Easter, Child toys, free catalog, summer, and picnics.

The Lakeside CollectionSM holds the privacy and security of our customers in the highest regard. The following data explains what kind of information is gathered on The Lakeside CollectionSM website and how the information is used. 

No information that we gather is shared with or sold to other organizations for any purposes.

The Lakeside CollectionSM will NOT rent, sell or trade the contents of our emailing list to any outside parties. You can be assured that your email address will be kept in strictest confidence. 

  * Does The Lakeside CollectionSM offer secure online ordering?
  * What kind of information do you collect from me when I visit your web site?
  * Does The Lakeside CollectionSM share information it collects from me with outside parties?
  * What are 'cookies' and how do you use them?
  * What do you do with my email address?
  * How else do you use information about me?
  * How do I remove my name from The Lakeside CollectionSM mailing list?

Does The Lakeside CollectionSM offer secure online ordering?

Yes, we do. All customer and order information is securely stored behind a firewall and protected from unauthorized access. Our secure server software, provided by Verisign, encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the internet. 

back to top

What kind of information do you collect from me when I visit your web site?

We do not collect any information from those merely visiting our site. We do ask for additional information if you would like to place an order, request an order status or a free catalog, or if you need to communicate with us regarding an account issue. 

back to top

Does The Lakeside CollectionSM share information it collects from me with outside parties?

Any information provided by a customer on the web site is used solely to fulfill a product order, a catalog request or research a customer inquiry. The information that you provide is stored in house (separate from the Internet) and is used exclusively to ensure fulfillment of your order, request or inquiry. 

back to top

What are 'cookies' and how do you use them?

'Cookies' are small bits of information that are sent from the Web server and kept on your browser. They are used by the Web server so it can remember who you are as you browse from page to page of our website. The cookie we send to your browser is not written to any file on your computer. It is only kept in memory and goes away when you exit your browser program. The content is simply a single number that helps us remember your order information. 

back to top

What do you do with my email address?

The Lakeside CollectionSM collects your email address as part of your registration with us. We use this address to communicate with you about your account. We do not sell or otherwise give out your email address to others. 

back to top

How else do you use information about me?

Once you make a purchase from us, you become a part of our customer file. As a valued Lakeside CollectionSM customer, you will be put on our mailing list to receive catalogs from us in the future. 

back to top

How do I remove my name from The Lakeside Collection'sSM mailing lists?

If, at any time, you wish to be removed from our mailing list please contact us by email with your name and address. 

back to top

Amendments to our Privacy Policy

In the event that lakeside.com amends its Privacy Policy in the future, these changes will be clearly posted on our website so you can be kept informed of how, where, when and why we collect information and how we use it. 

back to top
The Lakeside CollectionSM holds the privacy and security of our customers in the highest regard. The following data explains what kind of information is gathered on The Lakeside CollectionSM website and how the information is used. 

No information that we gather is shared with or sold to other organizations for any purposes.

The Lakeside CollectionSM will NOT rent, sell or trade the contents of our emailing list to any outside parties. You can be assured that your email address will be kept in strictest confidence. 

  * Does The Lakeside CollectionSM offer secure online ordering?
  * What kind of information do you collect from me when I visit your web site?
  * Does The Lakeside CollectionSM share information it collects from me with outside parties?
  * What are 'cookies' and how do you use them?
  * What do you do with my email address?
  * How else do you use information about me?
  * How do I remove my name from The Lakeside CollectionSM mailing list?

Does The Lakeside CollectionSM offer secure online ordering?

Yes, we do. All customer and order information is securely stored behind a firewall and protected from unauthorized access. Our secure server software, provided by Verisign, encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the internet. 

back to top

What kind of information do you collect from me when I visit your web site?

We do not collect any information from those merely visiting our site. We do ask for additional information if you would like to place an order, request an order status or a free catalog, or if you need to communicate with us regarding an account issue. 

back to top

Does The Lakeside CollectionSM share information it collects from me with outside parties?

Any information provided by a customer on the web site is used solely to fulfill a product order, a catalog request or research a customer inquiry. The information that you provide is stored in house (separate from the Internet) and is used exclusively to ensure fulfillment of your order, request or inquiry. 

back to top

What are 'cookies' and how do you use them?

'Cookies' are small bits of information that are sent from the Web server and kept on your browser. They are used by the Web server so it can remember who you are as you browse from page to page of our website. The cookie we send to your browser is not written to any file on your computer. It is only kept in memory and goes away when you exit your browser program. The content is simply a single number that helps us remember your order information. 

back to top

What do you do with my email address?

The Lakeside CollectionSM collects your email address as part of your registration with us. We use this address to communicate with you about your account. We do not sell or otherwise give out your email address to others. 

back to top

How else do you use information about me?

Once you make a purchase from us, you become a part of our customer file. As a valued Lakeside CollectionSM customer, you will be put on our mailing list to receive catalogs from us in the future. 

back to top

How do I remove my name from The Lakeside Collection'sSM mailing lists?

If, at any time, you wish to be removed from our mailing list please contact us by email with your name and address. 

back to top

Amendments to our Privacy Policy

In the event that lakeside.com amends its Privacy Policy in the future, these changes will be clearly posted on our website so you can be kept informed of how, where, when and why we collect information and how we use it. 

back to top
